A skeleton dating 200 years back
found in the Himalayas,
matched with the DNA
of his missing step-sister.
I want you to remember me
with those eyes of yours.
Always.
Kayoko Senba went to my uncle's house.
It wouldn't be this man, is it?
The body's all bones. No decomposing, either.
You must be admitted to a ward.
Wait!
Damn it...
[Yui Ishimizaki]
Where are you?
I need you here, now.
Haruka!
- Drive.
- Huh?
- Just drive!
- Okay, but please don't judge!
What happened?
I appreciate the help.
But you don't need to know.
Are you a wanted man or something?
I was set up.
They want me admitted to a ward.
Your father?
That's none of your business.
Hold on.
Maybe your father is involved in this case.
What?
He was a close friend of my uncle, right?
Ishimizaki may have been involved
in some trouble.
[Kyoichi Nanase]
It'll take a while longer
to identify the victim from this morning.
I'm not surprised,
seeing as they were all bones.
And the substance we found on the remains?
It was a unique mixture of substances.
The very same mixture that was
administered to Akihiko Ishimizaki.
The same culprit?
Most likely.
Same ol' mess, huh?
What were you looking into?
Nichie Pharmaceuticals.
The founder was involved in some deep shit.
[Yoichi Onodera]
Where the hell are you?
Hirama, of Toho Journal, yes?
Forget everything.
Who is this?
You're calling from Onodera's phone.
You'll find nothing in his desk.
I wanted to become a real journalist.
Sir, this is Maehara.
I don't believe he'll be
returning home today.
Yes, sir.
I knew it.
Your father must have something
he doesn't want you knowing about.
He's always on my case
when it comes to Shiharu.
Then your sister's disappearance
and my uncle's death are somehow relevant.
Haruka. You're still hiding
something from me, aren't you?
Have you witnessed anyone suspicious
around these parts?
I can't say I have.
Then have you noticed
anything amiss recently?
- Not really.
- I see.
- Got it.
- May I get going?
I have to go pick up my child.
Of course. Thank you for your cooperation.
What's up?
Those bones you found.
They were Yoichi Onodera's. I confirmed it.
Onodera?
Oh, that old wannabe reporter of yours.
He was a journalist.
Same difference. So, why was he killed?
Tell me how the investigation's going.
Share what you know, and I'll spill.
All I can say is that they're underway.
Then I have nothing more to tell you.
Please keep me updated in your findings.
Oikawa.
How's the wife doing?
You got a favor to ask?
- That obvious?
- Very.
Besides, I owe you for acting as our cupid.
So, what did you need?
Do you have any ties
to Nichie Pharmaceuticals?
Nichie Pharmaceuticals?
You write for finance.
I know you know a guy.
He doesn't support the CEO,
if you're alright with that.
Doesn't support him?
[DNA match to sample "T548"]
Is that really possible?
Those bones were from two centuries ago.
The STR multiplex system I utilized
is able to pick out one individual
from a set of several hundred trillion.
Then what?
Are we dealing with time travel here?
I know. He didn't believe me either.
That's why he wants me admitted.
Sorry.
Thankfully, I have a change of clothes here
for overnight stays.
Now I won't have to return home
for at least several more days.
Do you think Shiharu passed away?
I saw her.
I saw her during
my thesis presentation last year.
What was she like?
I want to know more about her.
Well...
She was an individual who cared
for children in faraway lands.
She cared for strangers she didn't even know.
We're cutting your hair because...
I'm donating it.
Some kids are genetically born without hair.
So people donate their hair,
and have wigs made for those kids.
People, like me.
- You'll donate your hair to a stranger?
- Yeah.
I want those kids to fight.
Against what?
Fate.
You sure about this?
Yeah. Get snipping!
Don't move.
Sorry.
- Ready?
- Yup.
Shiharu and I perceived the world
in very different ways.
She saw the world with kindness in her heart.
Someone must have tampered
with Shiharu's DNA sample.
It was most likely swapped with another,
by Professor Ishimizaki himself.
Why would my uncle do such a thing?
He may have been trying to tell me something.
Something regarding Shiharu.
Ishimizaki made the analysis himself.
[log.3]
I will deal with the aftermath swiftly.
Yes. He tampered with the sample.
There's simply no other explanation.
[The bones from two centuries ago
and his missing step-sister]
That's Kayoko Senba.
[S]
[Address]
I don't think she'd speak to us again.
Do not look into it any further.
I'll search her home.
- How?
- I'll figure something out.
Otherwise the Professor's message
will be lost on us.
This woman definitely knows something.
I'll walk you home.
No need, I'll be fine.
Are you planning to sleep on that couch?
Yeah, I'm used to it.
I've practically become an insomniac
in these past few years anyway.
I haven't managed to rest
since Mari has disappeared either.
But let's try. We have an early day tomorrow.
Right.
See you in the morning.
See you.
[Shigeru Takagi]
I understand you disagree
with the CEO, Mr. Takagi?
I have nothing but complaints about him.
Then let us eradicate
those complaints, together.
What?
Big fish are particularly susceptible
to media outlets working against them.
Kyoichi's no big fish.
He's merely the son of the late founder,
Yumihiko Nanase.
Kyoichi's main job
is cleaning up after his father.
How so?
By covering up his father's secrets.
Company image directly reflects the family.
It's the downside of a family business.
But if he's so desperate to save face,
Nichie is done for.
What about his father
is Kyoichi Nanase trying to hide?
His father was practically a tyrant.
Many were dissatisfied
with his way of management.
Did he misuse company revenue?
That's just one of the many
shady rumors surrounding him.
What other rumors have you heard of?
When it came to creating new medications,
he supposedly did so through...
dubious clinical studies.
Dubious studies...
As in, human experimentation?
That's just the rumor.
Treat it like an urban legend, if you will.
I see.
But allow me to say one thing.
From my experience,
no rumor is ever baseless.
I won't disclose my source, so please.
It's the Plantae.
The Plantae?
I can't say any more.
- Please be on your way.
- Mr. Takagi.
Look into the rest yourself.
Maybe you'll find yourself mixed up
with politicians from the MHLW.
The Ministry of Health, Labour and Welfare?
Thank you.
I will be in touch.
What are you doing here?
I heard this is a frequent spot of yours.
Especially when you have secrets to share.
Did the President have you tail me?
Is he keeping tabs on all his directors?
No. I'm only looking into those
who are of detriment to the company.
Know your place, boy.
I could say the very same to you, Mr. Takagi.
Or perhaps you're prepared
to lose that position of yours.
This laboratory is indeed suspicious.
They were operating without any issue,
only to shut down without warning.
And in the same year
as Yumihiko Nanase's passing.
Maybe this is a potential lead.
[Yoichi Onodera]
Hello? Is this Onodera?
Yes.
I appreciate your offer yesterday.
Do you remember who I am?
Yesterday?
I wish to speak about "you-know-what".
And that is?
I truly believe phones are a health risk.
But the country acts none the wiser to it.
Even now, wireless radiation...
I'm sorry for the private funeral.
I wanted to see her off with just us family.
She was out of contact
with her other relatives.
I'm sure this was fine.
Wrong. Try number two.
Well, when you get to a hundred, wake me up.
[Dear Haruka]
[My bones will simply return to Earth]
[I'm wishing you all the best]
Sorry. Did you want to be alone?
No, it's fine.
I always reread her letters here.
Do you, too?
No.
I see.
Father says he's moving back to Tokyo.
Yeah.
I'm going to stay here.
Then this might be the last movie
we ever watch together.
We were family.
But I guess that's over now.
Yeah.
There's no reason for Kyoichi to stay
now that Mom is gone.
He's worried about your health, too.
I'll be fine.
Especially thanks to this gift from Mom.
A knife?
Why?
It's to protect me.
From what?
The monster?
A monster chased me into the mountains
when I was younger.
Let's eat breakfast together!
- Of course.
- Keita!
- Is that okay?
- I told you not to barge in here.
- Can you eat natto?
- Yup!
- I can!
- Really?
- Yup.
- That's amazing.
- I'm so sorry.
- What else?
- I like eggs.
- And tomatoes?
Tomatoes? I don't know...
Sneaking in won't be easy.
I'm not sneaking in.
Oh, good.
Then how are you getting in,
while Kayoko Senba is out?
Kayoko Senba's husband, Kotaro,
was a botany professor
who passed away last year.
I'll pretend to be a former student,
and ask to pay my respects.
I see. Makes sense to me.
I want you to tail Kayoko Senba
when she leaves.
With the car?
If she takes a car, then yes.
Aw man...
- If it's too much...
- No.
I'll do it.
And you remember to smile, okay? Smile!
So, did you bring a gift to offer the family?
I'll go get one.
That's the sensible thing to do.
She's here.
Jump!
Nice job.
Take care.
[Chomei Publishing]
[Former Minister
of Health, Labour, and Welfare]
How was he, Hirama?
Find anything out about Nichie?
Yeah, he gave me a huge lead. Thanks.
What're you looking into now?
[Member of the Lower House, 32nd District]
"Discussing the budget
for developing new medicines".
[With Nichie Pharmaceutical's Kyoichi Nanase]
Who's that?
- Nanase?
- Yes.
We wish to ask him something.
I haven't seen him today.
Shall I try calling him?
His phone seems to be turned off.
He's not home either.
At the very least, he was here last night.
His change of clothes are gone, after all.
Is that so.
But none of our work now
requires staying overnight.
Since our advisor is gone and all.
Then what was Nanase doing?
Please don't touch that shelf.
We keep many dangerous chemicals there.
Such as?
Sodium dodecyl sulfate, for example.
A sulfate...
It's used for extracting DNA.
Do all students here
know how to utilize such chemicals?
Yes.
And the stolen skeleton...
Yes?
The one doing the analysis
was Haruka Nanase, correct?
Yes, sir.
Did you notice anything strange
about his procedures or actions?
No, he was following all protocol.
Haruka Nanase... He's definitely suspicious.
He has an alibi
for when the remains were stolen.
Does he really?
He had easy access to those bones.
He could've stolen them
at any other opportunity.
Then how did he tamper with
the security tapes?
I'm more concerned by the fact
that he's now gone missing.
Agreed.
- Call me if there's an emergency.
- Okay.
[Missed Calls - Kyoichi Nanase]
- Yes?
- Good afternoon.
My name is Inoue. I studied under
Kotaro Senba at Meicho University.
Since I was in the area,
I hoped to pay my respects to him.
I am grateful to the Professor, and...
Please, come on in.
Thank you.
Inoue.
Yes?
May I get your information in our guest book?
Of course.
[Takuya Inoue]
Were you close to my father-in-law?
Yes.
You're quite young. He must have passed away
while you were a new student.
He did, yes.
I'm sorry for interrogating.
Most who visit come for my mother-in-law.
It's not often we get a visitor
for my father-in-law.
The Professor, he...
Thinking back, he took great care of me.
I am truly grateful to him.
I see.
And here I thought
he only cared for his plants.
He was a funny man.
Pop quiz.
What are nucleic acids always accompanied by?
Basic proteins.
- Wrong.
- Huh?
- They're accompanied by nucleic 'bases'!
- What?
He would always make
the most confusing jokes.
Maybe fellow researchers like you
found them funny?
We'd give him a pity laugh or two.
Thought so.
Haruka.
Yes, sir?
You don't plan on staying on
as a researcher, do you?
- What?
- Don't worry, I take no offense.
Just promise me
you'll continue to believe in science.
Science is the pursuit of truth.
It's the unveiling of secrets.
Humans may lie, but science does not.
You must be quite popular on campus.
Will black tea do?
Excuse me.
Is Professor Kotaro's study
on the second floor?
Pardon?
The Professor once showed me a book
that now appears to be out of print.
If possible, I'd like to borrow it.
His books are all kept
in my mother-in-law's office.
We're technically not allowed inside
without her permission.
I think this bookshelf contains all his books.
Wow...
May I take my time to look through them?
Of course. Please stay as long as you'd like.
Is it alright if I leave you?
I have laundry to fold...
Of course. Go ahead.
Thank you.
[pass: kS9qz3m#]
[LOCKED]
[The aforementioned case]
[Dr. Senba]
[I've retrieved the bones]
[I am prepared to confront my sins]
[Akihiko Ishimizaki]
I knew it.
My father had no young students.
Shall I call the police?
I'm sorry. I came across a term
I had to look up.
Liar.
You could have used your phone.
My phone is out of battery.
I know a liar when I see one.
I reckon this is a fake name, too.
I'll just call your number to be sure.
Is Dr. Kayoko Senba really so great?
She looks down on all those below her.
As if those without smarts are human trash.
A heartless person like her,
studying genetics? I can't even laugh.
Do all researchers compete to see
who can tell the worst joke of all?
You're honest at heart.
What about her are you looking into?
Is she hiding something from us?
I can't say for sure.
Has she done something utterly heinous?
I wouldn't be surprised if she did.
[Mother-in-law]
[Yui Ishimizaki]
Mother, what's wrong?
Haruka, you have to run.
- Huh?
- What?
Haruka Nanase?
Wait!
Hey!
Let me out!
Please!
My mother gave her orders.
She said to hand you over to the police.
Let me explain myself!
I can't disobey my mother-in-law.
She's a terrifying woman,
who sees through everything.
Please, just listen to me!
My mother has already reported you.
I'm searching for my missing sister.
Kayoko Senba may know something
about her disappearance.
I apologize for lying to you,
but I had no other leads.
Mrs. Senba? Police.
Are you home?
Mrs. Senba?
Don't.
They'll get you.
Mrs. Senba?
Mrs. Senba, please answer us.
You're investigating my mother-in-law, yes?
Tell me anything you learn about her.
That's all I wish to know.
Alright.
The number that called you early is mine.
Promise to stay in touch, okay?
Okay.
Let's talk at length next time.
Coming.
Haruka, you're safe! Thank goodness.
What about you? Everything okay?
I'm sorry. She noticed I was tailing her.
Please stop this.
I already know Nanase's boy is at my place.
I'll report him to the police.
If I see you again, you're next.
She knew all about our plan.
How?
I don't know. I'm just glad you're okay.
I managed to find an email
Professor Ishimizaki sent to Kayoko Senba.
Really? What did it say?
"I've retrieved the bones".
"I am prepared to confront my sins".
Sins?
The professor committed some taboo
involving the bones from Roopkund.
But he was prepared to accept his sins.
To face one's sins. In other words...
He was prepared to atone?
Exactly.
To atone usually means to confess.
But the Professor
was never given that chance.
He was killed before he could.
He sent Kayoko Senba that email
despite the risks. Why?
I can think of two possible reasons.
Either she was a victim, or...
She was an accomplice.
I'm still not sure which.
Maybe my uncle was trying to tell you
about this sin of his.
Science is the pursuit of truth.
It's the unveiling of secrets.
Humans may lie, but science does not.
[Shiharu Nanase]
Shiharu is involved
in this sin of his.
We have to find what ties the Professor
and Kayoko Senba together.
I'm right by Kanzawa Central Library.
I'll do some digging there.
Shiharu.
What?
What is it?
I love you.
[Darwin]
[Kayoko Senba]
[Search]
[ROOPKUND]
Do you recall that nosey journalist, Onodera?
Apparently his corpse has turned up.
Those folks at Nichie Pharmaceuticals
may be taking drastic measures.
Good evening, Haruka Nanase.
I am known...
as Ushio.
You have gotten too involved.
Pardon?
You are too involved
in the mysteries surrounding Roopkund.
I am only searching for my missing sister.
[A Challenge to Roopkund Lake]
Sir.
Your visitor has arrived.
This is...
You...
You killed Ishimizaki, did you not?
Even if you managed to find your sister,
I would simply devour her.